National Railroad Adjustment Board Case Files 5837
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Docket No. 33677. Award No. 17608. Southern Pacific Co. Harold Ferguson., 1956-1957 (Box 67, Folder 39)
- Docket No. 33739. Award No. 18859. Southern Pacific. Senior Men., 1956 (Box 67, Folder 40)
- Docket No. 33764. Award No. 19008. Southern Pacific Co. Yard Helper., 1949-1956 (Box 67, Folder 41)
- Docket No. 33767. Award No. 18709. Northern Pacific Terminal Co. ER Goodrich., 1956-1958 (Box 67, Folder 42)
- Docket No. 33797. Award No. 18873. Los Angeles Junction. Joint Submission., 1956-1958 (Box 67, Folder 43)
- Docket No. 33804. Award No. 19009. Southern Pacific. Helpers Shields Tricker., 1954-1956 (Box 67, Folder 44)
- Docket No. 33822. Award No. 19010. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad. Monte H Phillips. Joint Submission., 1956-1958 (Box 67, Folder 45)
- Docket No. 33823. Award No. 19011. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific. JE Whitley., 1956 (Box 67, Folder 46)
- Docket No. 33889. Award No. 19021. Southern Pacific. Whitlow, van Hardenburg, O'Donald, Houdashelt, Tausch., 1956-1959 (Box 67, Folder 47)
- Docket No. 33900. Award No. 19022. Southern Pacific. Claim of Yard Helper., 1950-1959 (Box 67, Folder 48)
- Docket No. 33928. Award No. 19039. Southern Pacific. HW Bird, Helpers Sneer and Hougak., 1956 (Box 67, Folder 49)
- Docket No. 33937. Award No. 18261. Southern Pacific. TP Wilson., 1955-1956 (Box 67, Folder 50)
- Docket No. 33980. Award No. 18109. Southern Pacific. RW Claassen., 1945-1956 (Box 67, Folder 51)
- Docket No. 33981. Award No. 18986. Southern Pacific. WG Martinsen et al., 1954-1956 (Box 67, Folder 52)
- Docket No. 33991. Award No. 18985. Southern Pacific. JW Shields., 1954-1956 (Box 67, Folder 53)
- Docket No. 34032. Award No. 18987. Southern Pacific. LC Byrnes., 1955-1956 (Box 67, Folder 54)
- Docket No. 34066. Award No. 18988. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific. Joint Submission., 1953-1956 (Box 67, Folder 55)
- Docket No. 34067. Award No. 18989. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific. Joint Submission., 1956 (Box 67, Folder 56)
- Docket No. 34068. Award No. 19018. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific. Joint Submission., 1956-1959 (Box 67, Folder 57)
- Docket No. 34069. Award No. 19022. Southern Pacific. WE Bodle et al., 1956 (Box 67, Folder 58)
- Docket No. 34069. Award No. 19019. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific. Switchmen Pay., 1959 (Box 67, Folder 59)
- Docket No. 34107. Award No. 19163. Los Angeles Junction Railway. Everly, Downey, Shedd., 1954-1956 (Box 67, Folder 60)
- Docket No. 34112. Award No. 19164. Southern Pacific. TV O'Donald., 1955-1959 (Box 67, Folder 61)
- Docket No. 34114. Award No. 19150. Southern Pacific. Shay-Phelan, Mears., 1956 (Box 67, Folder 62)
- Docket No. 341117. Award No. 19151. Southern Pacific. Robinson, Price, Justice., 1959 (Box 67, Folder 63)
- Docket No. 34171. Award No. 19152. WW Kasner, Helpers Huml and Mildenberger., 1954-1957 (Box 67, Folder 64)
- Docket No. 34172. Award No. 19221. Southern Pacific. One Day's Pay., 1956-1957 (Box 67, Folder 65)
- Docket No. 34186. Award No. 21027. Chicago Great Western. RH Gott, Helpers LL Ladd, PJ Schlmeiser., 1965-1967 (Box 67, Folder 66)
- Docket No. 34187. Award No. 29940. Chicago Great Western. FA Ruby, et al., 1956-1966 (Box 67, Folder 67)
- Docket No. 34201. Award No. 19131. Southern Pacific. Dunn., 1957-1959 (Box 67, Folder 68)
- Docket No. 34202. Award No. 19132. Southern Pacific Co. PA Trice., 1956-1957 (Box 67, Folder 69)
- Docket No. 34202. Award No. 19132. Southern Pacific Co. PA Trice, El Paso Yard., 1955 (Box 67, Folder 70)
- Docket No. 34223. Award No. 19133. Southern Pacific. Three Senior Men., 1956-1957 (Box 67, Folder 71)
- Docket No. 34224. Award No. 18904. Western Pacific Railroad Co. AH Harper., 1955-1959 (Box 67, Folder 72)
- Docket No. 34226. Award No. 19179. Southern Pacific. Bodle, Horick, Ranck., 1954-1959 (Box 67, Folder 73)
- Docket No. 34250. Award No. 19141. Southern Pacific. H Higuera., 1957-1959 (Box 67, Folder 74)
- Docket No. 34255. Award No. 19142. Southern Pacific Co. JW Buell., 1949-1957 (Box 67, Folder 75)
- Docket No. 34359. Award No. 20927. Los Angeles Junction. AJ Singer, Helpers OJ Lewis and VS Goss., 1959-1966 (Box 67, Folder 76)
- Docket No. 34495. Award No. 2028. Los Angeles Junction. HM Everly., 1957 (Box 67, Folder 77)
- No. 35257. Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  May 13 1958.
- No. 35257. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Don A Miller., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- No. 35258. Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Don A Miller., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- No. 35258. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  May 13 1958
- No. 35259. Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived., 1958-1960 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- No. 35259. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- No. 35260. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Don A Miller. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- No. 35260. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- No. 35261. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 9)
- No. 35261. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Don A Miller. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 10)
- No. 35262. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Don A Miller. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 11)
- No. 35262. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 12)
- No. 35263. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Don A Miller. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 13)
- No. 35263. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived, 1958 (Box 68, Folder 14)
- No. 35264. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Don A Miller. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 15)
- No. 35264. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 16)
- No. 35265. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 17)
- No. 35265. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 18)
- No. 35266. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 19)
- No. 35266. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 20)
- No. 35267. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 21)
- No. 35267. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 22)
- No. 35268. Delaware Lackawanna and Western. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 23)
- No. 35268. Delaware Lackawanna and Pacific. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 24)
- No. 35269. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Don A Miller. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 25)
- No. 35269. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 26)
- No. 35270. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Don A Miller. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 27)
- No. 35270. Delaware Lackawanna and Western. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 28)
- No. 35271. Delaware Lackawanna and Western. Don A Miller. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 29)
- No. 35271. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 30)
- No. 35272. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Don A Miller. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 31)
- No. 35272. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 32)
- No. 35273. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 33)
- No. 3523. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 34)
- No. 35274. Delaware Lackawanna and Western. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 35)
- No. 35274. Delaware Lackawanna and Western. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 36)
- No. 35275. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 37)
- No. 35275. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 38)
- No. 35276. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 39)
- No. 3526. Delaware Lackawanna and Western. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 40)
- No. 35277. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 41)
- No. 35277. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 42)
- No. 35278. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 43)
- No. 35278. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 44)
- No. 35279. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 45)
- No. 35279. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 46)
- No. 3528. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 47)
- No. 35280. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 48)
- No. 35281. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 49)
- No. 35281. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 50)
- No. 35282. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 51)
- No. 35282. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 52)
- No. 35283. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 53)
- No. 35283. Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 54)
- No. 35285. Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 55)
- No. 35285. Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 56)
- No. 35287. Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 57)
- No. 35287. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 58)
- No. 35288. Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 59)
- No. 35288. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 60)
- No. 35614. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 61)
- No. 35614. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1958 (Box 68, Folder 62)
- No. 36558. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 63)
  July 22 1959.
- No. 36558. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 64)
- No. 36559. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 65)
- No. 36559. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 66)
- No. 3650. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 67)
- No. 36560. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 68)
- No. 36561. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 69)
- No. 36561. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 70)
- No. 36562. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 71)
  July 22 1959
- No. 36562. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 72)
- No. 36563. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 73)
- No. 36563. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 74)
- No. 36564. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 75)
- No. 36564. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 76)
- No. 36565. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 77)
- No. 36565. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 78)
- No. 36566. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 79)
- No. 36566. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 80)
- No. 3587. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 81)
  July 30 1959
- No. 36587. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 82)
- No. 36588. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 83)
- No. 36588. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 84)
- No. 36605. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived. Don A Miller., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 85)
  August 11 1959
- No. 36605. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived. CW Kealey., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 86)
- No. 36606. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Hearing Waived., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 87)
- No. 36606. Delaware Lackawanna and Western Railroad. SUNA. Don A Miller., 1959 (Box 68, Folder 88)
- Docket No. 34555. Award No. 18563. Great Northern Railway Co. EJ Callan., 1957-1958 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Docket No. 34565. Award No. 21040. New Orleans Terminal Co. AJ Danner, Joly Gavin., 1957-1967 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Docket No. 34588. Award No. 18564. Fort Worth and Denver Railway Co. JH Dillard., 1956-1958 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Docket No. 34631. Award No. 18659. Southern Pacific Co. TJ Dominick., 1955-1957 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Docket No. 34657. Award No. 18660. Southern Pacific. Switchman CH Swanson., 1955-1957 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Docket No. 34787. Award No. 19153. Denver and Rio Grande Western Railroad Co. DD Jordan., 1957 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Docket No. 34974. Award No. 18841. New Orleans and North Eastern Railroad Co. Carl E Draughn., 1955-1959 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Docket No. 34799. Award No. 20935. Western Pacific. DS Valencia., 1957-1966 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Docket No. 35145. Award No. 18904. Southern Pacific. EQ Payne. El Paso Yard., 1957-1958 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Docket No. 35150. Award No. 18905. Southern Pacific Co. Harry F Dodd, Oakland Yard., 1958 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Docket No. 35366. Award No. 20914. Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer Railway Co., 1958 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- Docket No. 36717. Award No. 19477. Western Pacific Railroad Company. Neil D Futch., 1959 (Box 69, Folder 12)
- Docket No. 36992. Award No. 20074. Union Depot Company Columbus. RJ Nolan., 1959-1962 (Box 69, Folder 13)
- Docket No. 36995. Award No. 19910. Kansas City Terminal Railway Co. JD Mitchell., 1959-1961 (Box 69, Folder 14)
- Docket No. 37100. Award No. 19968. Western Pacific Railroad. AT Powers., 1958-1960 (Box 69, Folder 15)
- Docket No. 37653. Award No. 20037. Northern Pacific Terminal Co. EB Jones., 1960 (Box 69, Folder 16)
- Docket No. 37846. Award No. 20126. Southern Pacific. FA Wallery., 1959-1960 (Box 69, Folder 17)
- Award No. 20237. Docket No. 38002. Southern Pacific. Workman., 1961-1963 (Box 69, Folder 18)
- Award No. 20474. Docket No. 38656. Southern Pacific. AF Habert., 1964 (Box 69, Folder 19)
- Award No. 20499. Docket No. 38889. Southern Pacific. JL Brown., 1962-1964 (Box 69, Folder 20)
- Award No. 20511. Docket No. 38897. Southern Pacific Co. EC Duff., 1962-1965 (Box 69, Folder 21)
- Award No. 20611. Docket No. 39299. Southern Pacific Co. GV Howard., 1960-1963 (Box 69, Folder 22)
- Award No. 20865. Docket No. 39553. Southern Pacific. Walsh., 1966 (Box 69, Folder 23)
- Award No. 20929. Docket No. 39570. Central of Georgia Railway Co. Hugh Lott and CT Rochester., 1963 (Box 69, Folder 24)